No, thank you!
We're good!
(string instruments playing
"Bridal Chorus")
(Sheldon:)Raj, you're probably wondering
(Sheldon:)why Amy and I aren't showing
any affection to one another.
(Raj:)Didn't even crack the top ten.
(Sheldon:)Well, you should know
(Sheldon:)that she recently
broke up with me.
(Amy:)I said I needed
time to think.
(Raj:)I'm sure you guys
will figure something out.
(Sheldon:)You hear that?
Raj is devastated.
(Bernadette:)Sheldon, shh.
The wedding's starting.
(Sheldon:)I see what's happening.
(Sheldon:)Sides are forming.
(Sheldon:)Well, if Bernadette's
on Amy's team, I pick Howard.
(Howard:)I'm not taking sides.
(Sheldon:)Fine, I guess
I'm stuck with Raj.
(Raj:)Really?
(Stuart:)At least you
got picked.
(Official:)Before I go any further,
(Official:)have either of you
prepared your own vows?
(Sheldon:)Yes.
No.
(Penny:)You wrote vows?
(Sheldon:)Yeah.
(Penny:)Well, I don't have any.
(Penny:)You're kind of
making me look bad.
It's okay. I-I don't
have to say them.
(Penny:)No, no, no, go ahead.